вжд╩
Yo, Chunk, right on time, dude.
I slept in your driveway
вжд╩
so I wouldn't be late.
Whoa. That's hard core, bro.
вжд╩
Load it, drive it, rig it, repeat.
That's the life of a rock and roll roadie, isn't it?
вжд╩
'Ello, 'ello, Chunk.
Pip, pip, cheerio--oh!
вжд╩
Don't mind my dad.
He spent one semester abroad,
вжд╩
and he thinks he's a Brit.
That's all right, love.
вжд╩
Wotcha, me China.
All the Mae West to the Duchess of Fife
вжд╩
and the wee dustbin lids too.
Uh... Right!
вжд╩
Uh, couldn't agree more!
Catch ya later, Pop Star.
вжд╩
Good luck with your audition, honey!
"Wee dustbin lids."
вжд╩
That must be in here somewhere.
Dropping records on a weekly basis
вжд╩
Playing shows in exotic places
Rocking out to a cheering crowd
вжд╩
Hear them screaming, "Luna Loud!"
My favorite colors are platinum and gold
вжд╩
Being a rock star never gets old
My life is a dream
вжд╩
A crazy rock and roll dream
Stage dive!
вжд╩
Sorry, dude.
I hope I passed the audition.
вжд╩
Oh, you did more than pass.
You're gonna be headlining the Royal Rumble.
вжд╩
Congratulations, dear.
Smashing, love! Your biggest gig yet!
вжд╩
Whoo! Next stop, rock and roll fame!
- Is--is that Chester Monk? - The one and only.
вжд╩
Great to see you, Ms. Vaporciyan.
Whoa! You know Chunk?
вжд╩
Well, I was his first teacher
when he moved here from England.
вжд╩
I always thought he was gonna be such a big rock star.
You know, he headlined the Rumble too.
вжд╩
He did?
Why didn't you tell me you headlined the Rumble, dude?
вжд╩
Didn't wanna toot me own horn,
but yeah, it was quite a show.
вжд╩
Five encores, but who's counting?
Have a butcher's at me yearbook.
вжд╩
"Next stop, rock and roll fame"?
Next stop, rock and roll fame!
вжд╩
Great minds think alike, eh, love?
'Ello, governor.
вжд╩
Just what I was fancying.
Why is he grabbing that junk off the road?
вжд╩
What if I don't make it as a rock star?
I don't wanna end up living in a van, man.
вжд╩
So, uh, why do you wanna work in a record store?
Well, I really wanted to be a rock star,
вжд╩
but that's probably never gonna happen,
so I figured this is another way
вжд╩
I can share my love of music with people.
Right on.
вжд╩
You're hired.
Welcome, dude! How can I help you?
вжд╩
Do you have Mick Swagger's new album?
I hear he's pretty good.
вжд╩
Pretty good? Mick's basically a rock god!
But you can't just start with his new stuff.
вжд╩
You need to know where the man's coming from.
Let's start with his first album,
вжд╩
"Where I'm Coming From."
This is Mick's fifth album, where he went reggae.
вжд╩
If you play it backwards, it's a country album,
so it's actually his fifth and sixth.
вжд╩
Mick's ninth album is super rare,
'cause instead of vinyl, they made it out of hard candy.
вжд╩
Luna, you gotta chill out.
Dude, I'm with a customer.
вжд╩
You mean that customer?
Hey, I love your enthusiasm, kid,
вжд╩
but it's also why I'm firing you.
So, I figure, this is another way
вжд╩
I can share my love of music with people.
Cool. You're my new afternoon DJ.
вжд╩
Ooh, girl, if I could
Ooh, girl, give you the--
вжд╩
Ooh, girl, if I could - Yeah, girl, sing it!
Ooh, girl, if I could
вжд╩
Ooh, ooh, la, la, la
Ooh, girl! World girl!
вжд╩
You girl!
Greetings, third eldest sister.
вжд╩
Just making the rounds for my weekly DNA cheek swabs.
I don't typically acknowledge human emotions,
вжд╩
but you seem unusually dispirited.
You're too young to understand.
вжд╩
Pfft, tell that to the Nobel Committee.
Respect.
вжд╩
Well, I'm worried about my future, dude.
Making it as a rock star seems impossible,
вжд╩
but I can't find a fit anywhere else in the music business.
I just don't know what to do now.
вжд╩
I would advise a practical approach.
According to national labor statistics,
вжд╩
the fastest growing fields are health care,
food service, and technology.
вжд╩
I suggest you delve into those.
I hear what you're laying down, Sis.
вжд╩
Wish me luck.